You know the fairy tale
about the princess
waiting for some brave prince
to come and save her?
Yeah, this is not that kind of a story.
Meet Samantha.
She's the second-born daughter
of the royal family of Illyria,
the smallest country in Europe.
See? That one right there.
Sam, here,
has never been a typical princess.
Unlike her older sister, Eleanor,
who always seemed perfectly regal
in every way,
Sam wasn't.
Things got even tougher when, at age
five, she found out her father, the king,
had died in a plane crash
with his brother.
After that, Sam's mom took over the throne
and the job of running the country.
But in a few weeks,
Eleanor, the rightful heir,
will turn 18,
and she'll become the Queen of Illyria.
As for Sam, she's just never fit
into this royal world.
She's like so many second-borns
just searching for her place.
You see, Sam's destined for great things.
She just doesn't know it yet.
That's where I come in.
But... we'll get there soon enough.
We're almost there.
Good, 'cause this gear is not light.
Tell me about it.
Hey, are you sure you wanna do this?
-Last chance to turn back.
- Of course I'm sure.
You sound like my mom.
Come on.
Do you know how many people
would kill to be royalty? I would.
You so do not mean that.
You can do whatever you want
with your life.
You can just be yourself.
My entire future is planned out for me.
Second-borns are supposed
to host cocktail parties
and cut ribbons
and smile silently in the background.
It's not me.
I wanna do something that matters.
Makes sense to me.
-Hello, Illyria.
-
We are here because we want change.
Down with the monarchy.
Give us freedom.
We demand a voice. A choice.
If you agree with us,
make some noise. Hit it!
And what you need
It's time that everybody speak
To see what we see
-
-Do you hear that?
-What?
We gotta go. You get the gear.
I'll distract the cops.
Hey, hey, hey! Get back here!
88-14 clear.
-Leave us.
-Your Majesty.
Hey, Mom.
Again, Samantha?
You're in here
planning Eleanor's coronation,
but out there people are unhappy.
No, some people, about 30 of them.
It's a flash mob, not a majority.
-The rest are content.
-Really?
Hate it or not, you are a princess,
and if you could just stop rebelling
against that,
you might realize that
it's actually a pretty cool opportunity.
Whatever. I gotta go to school.
Don't forget to wash your face.
I'm 15. I don't need to be told--
Thanks.
Good morning, young royals.
Summer break is almost here,
but not quite yet. Get to class.
So, Gwenyth124 asked me why I
was spending my summer vacation in Haiti.
And it's because I saw this video
of these adorable, unfortunate orphans.
They were caught in a mudslide, and I just
knew that I had to do something, you know?
I got to go. Love. Bye.
It wasn't a mudslide.
It was a 7.0 earthquake
followed by a Category 4 hurricane.
Yes, a hurricane that caused a mudslide.
And, besides, I don't think it really
matters why the Haitians are suffering.
The point is that I'm there
to do something about it.
-Which is what exactly?
-Oh, I'm building an orphanage.
Will you be carrying bricks,
pouring concrete?
I'm a princess. I'm bringing awareness.
To Haiti, or to yourself?
Listen, this is more
than you've ever done for anyone.
You just walk around hating on
the monarchy and embarrassing your family.
Your sister must be so ashamed
to be related to you.
That's why I have 106 million friends,
and you have none.
Level four
is the worst of the worst.
The most notorious criminals in the world.
Inmates ordinary prisons
aren't equipped to handle.
-What's on level five?
-We call him Inmate 34.
All this for one guy? Who is he?
Don't know. I'm not sure I want to.
That was good.
Still think we can do better.
Well, now that it's summer,
we've got way more time to practice.
No more school.
No more Roxana, Princess von Selfie.
Oh, it's so cool she's going to Haiti.
Thank you.
Look, the point is,
we have our first paid gig coming up,
and for us to be ready, we need to focus.
Oh, I am focused. It is going to be
the highlight of my summer.
Not necessarily.
To celebrate your release from Strathmore
School for the Incredibly Entitled
and mine from Illyria Public,
I got us tickets to...
-I'm not worthy.
-Your dad's gonna let you go?
-Well, he's working all night.
Luckily, coronations
keep a groundskeeper very busy.
I will see you there.
Oh, and you might want to brush
your teeth.
I can smell
the garlic naan you had for lunch.
That was... two days ago.
Uh...
Did you know
that every snowflake is unique...
each with its imperfections and flaws?
That's what makes them so special.
You're my snowflake, Sam.
Samantha!
Why aren't you ready? We're gonna be late.
Late for what?
Thank you,
Illyrian foreign press.
Thank you so much for coming.
Hey. You look wonderful.
Thank you for coming.
I apologize for being late.
It's not your fault.
You know,
the Queen does have the authority
to imprison someone for tardiness.
Well, you're not the queen yet.
Four weeks.
I can hardly wait.
And if being in a dungeon means
I don't have to wear this dress, then--
A photo of Your Majesties?
-Thank you.
-
I gotta go.
I have a huge headache
and a massive history final tomorrow.
Your Highness,
Duke Heresford.
Straight home. Study and sleep.
Thank you.
Have a good prom.
-Boo!
-Finally. I thought you ghosted me.
It's Bramblebone.
Nothing in the world could stop me.
IDs?
I can't believe this.
Must be a new rule.
How was I supposed to know
that they card now?
-Come on. I have an idea.
-
Wha-- How did you do that?
I saw the guy enter the code.
Right. Yeah, that totally makes sense.
You could see those tiny numbers
from super far away.
Which brings me back to,
how did you do that?
I don't know. It's weird.
Let's go. They're playing a new song.
It's so good!
- I love this song!
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
-
Are you okay?
I need to make it stop.
-
What was that?
We've been Bramble-banned for life.
I don't know.
It was like I was hearing every
single sound in the club all at once.
Even the wings on a fly.
It sounds crazy.
Well, not coming from the girl
who can make out the numbers on a keypad
from across the street
and smell what I had for lunch
two days ago.
Maybe I have a brain tumor.
You don't have a brain tumor, Sam.
You know what I thought
when I first saw you ten years ago?
Why is she hot-wiring my dad's tractor?
That you were gonna be my best friend.
Although, the hot-wiring thing was--
It's pretty sick.
I'm here for you, Sam.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You're gonna be fine.
-This sucks.
- I'm sorry.
-
Hey... Dad!
You missed your history final.
Professor Blake will let me make it up.
No one will know anything about
what happened last night,
especially not my... mom.
You knew? And you let me
spend the night in jail?
Actions have consequences.
It's a miracle the only casualty
was the band's sound system,
which is coming out of your allowance.
Of course.
-I spoke to Professor Blake.
He'll let you make up the final
by attending summer school.
-No way!
-Very much "way."
You'll live on campus. No distractions.
Am I clear?
Good. Go pack.
-School starts...
-Tomorrow?
I know.
Guess I can't complain
about being grounded for the weekend.
So much for our first gig.
I will find a way to escape.
-Oh. I gotta go.
The person of the year
just walked into my room.
Okay, bye.
-I came to say goodbye.
-You mean good riddance?
The next time we see each other--
You'll be Queen.
Like you've always wanted.
I wish you could be happy for me.
I want to.
But I don't understand
how any of this can make you happy.
Always being on display.
Being told exactly how to be.
We're royals.
That's our job.
I know it makes sense to you.
It just never has for me.
Maybe someday it will.
Hello?
I'm free.
The apple was a very clever idea.
Stick to the plan.
Phase one begins tomorrow.
Summer school students,
please report to room 203.
Hi, there.
Uh, hi, there.
Heard you the first time.
Oh, I wasn't sure.
I'm January.
I'm Palace School back in Luxembourg.
Just here for the extra credit.
You must be Sam.
Our royal families go way back.
My dad was friends with your uncle.
I heard Strathmore is the best.
It sucks.
You'll love it.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
-So...
-Look, June--
-January.
- Whatever.
You seem like a perfectly typical princess
who's genuinely excited to be here.
I just figured since we were
the only two people in the class...
Oh, hi. I didn't notice you.
-I'm January, this is--
-Sam.
I'm Matteo.
Nice to meet you--
What's up, breakfast club?
So, this is Strathmore?
My fourth school in three months.
Bad news, you're stuck here.
Good news, you're stuck here with me.
How exactly is that "good news"?
'Cause I bring the party, Joan of Dark.
Drop dead, Fresh Prince.
It's all right. She'll come
around. I tend to grow on people.
-Like fungus?
-Yeah.
It's so good to see you guys.
All 108 million of you.
Thank you, Evil Kitten, and no, I'm not
looking forward to summer school either.
But I am a survivor.
Right, gotta run. Loves.
I can't believe this is happening.
Fourteen days of unexcused absence.
I mean,
I Skyped in every day from Coachella.
I didn't know you could be sent to
summer school for having no fashion sense.
-Go mute yourself.
-Ouch.
Hi, Roxana.
I'm a really big fan.
I'm January, and I can't wait
to get to know all of you better.
Well, I'll give you the CliffsNotes.
She's the most annoying person in school,
and Prince Tuma over here,
is a total jerk.
He dated my BFF,
and all he cares about is himself.
And all you care about
is what filter you use.
I've always been no filter,
and everyone knows that.
Where's the rest of the class?
There can't only be four of us.
-Five.
- Good morning, class.
My name's Mr. Morrow,
but you can call me James.
Yup, this is me.
Your loyal royal narrator.
I bet you were wondering
when I'd show up.
Little bit about me.
I have a boyfriend named Henry,
an iguana named Jeff,
and a severe gluten allergy.
Seriously, give me a bagel
and I'm as good as dead.
We are going to have fun this summer.
Oh, God. We got the "cool teacher."
Thank you.
No one's ever called me cool before.
This ain't my first rodeo.
You guys are in good hands.
He definitely wasn't the cool teacher.
Quick question for you.
Why do you think you're here?
Oh, well, I threw a party.
That doesn't sound bad.
In the chem lab,
burned down half the school.
-It wasn't my fault.
- Incorrect.
Prince Matteo, same question.
Um...
My parents got a letter from school.
My social skills are a bit lacking.
The principal thought
a smaller class might help.
Also, incorrect. Princess Samantha.
It's Sam,
and I'm pretty sure anything I say
is gonna be wrong.
Now, that is correct.
The reasons all of you
were sent to "summer school"
were cover-up stories to get you
all here without arousing suspicion.
I get it.
I'm on a reality TV show.
Are you the host?
Oh, no. Gosh. That's the dream, though.
But, alas, I'm a prince.
A second-born royal, just like you guys.
Our siblings are the heirs, we the spares.
Powerless.
Without purpose...
or so everyone thinks.
Dude, you're a hologram.
They had one of Celine Dion performing
at my cousin's knighting ceremony.
Maybe it's a twin brother?
Okay, here's the deal.
There's a special gene exclusive
to second-borns of royal bloodlines.
A gene that gives some of us
extraordinary abilities
that manifest at your age.
You guys have superpowers.
Your abilities are unique to you alone.
That is why you're here,
to harness your untapped potential,
which you will use as members of
the Secret Society of Second-Born Royals.
It's a mouthful, we know.
we're superheroes?
That's correct.
There is one catch, though.
Nobody, even your family,
can know we exist.
I've had that superpower for years.
Dude, so sad.
Now, to protect our secrecy,
I'm going to have to take
all of your phones.
I'm so sorry to confiscate your phones
for the immediate
and not so temporary future.
When you say, "the immediate
and not so temporary future,"
you don't mean, like,
the whole summer, right?
The pain you're experiencing right now
will only make you stronger.
So, James,
are you the head of the Society?
Not exactly.
I am.
Mom?
Welcome to
the Secret Society training program.
For thousands of years,
second-borns like you and myself
have protected our kingdoms from threats,
assassins and international criminals.
We work in secret.
Our rewards? Lives saved. Order restored.
The next six weeks will be challenging.
You may doubt you have what it takes,
but whatever obstacles you face,
nothing is impossible.
Those of you who make the cut
will join the Society.
Those who don't
will return to your kingdoms.
You'll be stripped of your powers,
and your memories will be modified to
erase any recollection of this training.
I wish you the best of luck.
You lied to me.
I withheld the truth.
There's a difference.
Did Dad know? Does El?
No, and she'll never know.
That's how we protect those we love.
How?
You long to be more than a princess,
this meaningless title you were born with.
This is your chance.
Go join the others and make me proud.
What did you tell her?
- What she needed to hear.
Any news on the prison break?
He had help.
Every Society operative around the world
is out searching. We'll find him.
Do you have something for me?
Not yet, but I'm working on it.
Meanwhile, keep strengthening
your telekinesis. It's been a long time.
I rotted in that cell Catherine put me in
for ten years...
waiting to escape
while the world forgot I existed.
Now I'm going to take everything from her.
Ten years.
Welcome, trainees.
Now you're probably all wondering,
"What are my powers?"
I'm wondering that myself,
but we will get to that.
First, however, a little Secret Society
tradition for new trainees.
You're gonna like it.
Actually, you might not like it.
What's up?
Does that involve push-ups?
I have a doctor's note for that.
All right.
Yeah, you're definitely not gonna like it.
No way. This is amazing!
Super basic. All you gotta do
is get from here to there.
First person who gets the pyramid
wins the prize.
Piece of cake.
Lesson one, expect the unexpected.
Well, what are you waiting for,
a royal invitation? Let's go.
FYI, the lasers hurt.
Whoop.
I'm going to beat you.
- You wish.
Ah, you kids are really athletic.
Ow, I chipped a nail.
Guys, I just lost my thumb.
I text with my thumb.
Oh, my God. I'm melting.
-That's your power. Invisibility.
-A-plus.
Can I have my legs back now?
They're my second
most-commented-on feature.
You just lost your bottom.
Right, that's it. I'm out.
Hey, forget her. Help me up.
Coming.
So demanding.
Figure out this course
and take me to the pyramid.
Why do I suddenly care so much
about helping you?
Because I'm charming.
Not to anyone with a pulse.
Maybe that's his power? He tells people
what to do, and they listen.
Fine.
Tell me your most embarrassing secret.
I've never kissed anyone.
You see, I'd never admit that.
He can make people do whatever he says.
Greatest power ever.
Duck!
Lesson two, be aware of your surroundings.
It would be really useful
if you gave us the lessons beforehand.
Well, that would kinda defeat
the whole purpose, wouldn't it?
A word of warning,
the lasers are still shooting.
How did you know?
I heard it. I have super senses.
Whoa!
-How did you do that?
-The laser bounced off the padding.
-
Ow.
Can I have my cell phone back, please?
-Well, that was a great success.
-
Does anyone want to trade powers?
Super senses for kind of invisibility?
I'm good.
What about you, Matteo?
You're kind of invisible anyway.
Sure. You can have my power
of being awkward
'cause that's all I have right now.
So many bugs.
Maybe we're late bloomers.
We just have to be patient.
-Just like that story about the tortoise--
-Stop talking.
Well, that was rude.
I just wanted to see if it'll work.
And January was annoying me.
Can you order yourself
to be less obnoxious?
Hey, that was a joke. Come on.
You don't have much
to freak out about, anyway.
Your mom's the boss.
You're in no matter what.
You seriously overestimate
my relationship with my mother.
Oh, my God. Guys, you can see me, right?
Everything except your face.
What's wrong with my face?
Where'd January go?
Dunno.
But I can see your face again.
Hmm?
It doesn't make sense.
James said our powers are unique,
and we already have an invisible girl.
Not anymore.
-Ow!
Ugh, really?
-You slapped me.
-You deserved it.
Ooh, I can talk again.
-Slap yourself.
-No, you slap yourself.
-Ow!
-Why did you do that?
She told me to do it.
I'm so confused.
When January touched Roxana,
she became invisible,
and when she touched Tuma,
he did exactly what she told him to.
So, whoever I touch last...
You take away their power,
and it becomes yours.
Great. Now I'm the only person
without a power.
Typical.
Hey, you're going to find your power too,
and it's gonna be awesome.
Really think so?
Yeah.
Totally.
I hope it's X-ray vision... or flying.
Well, flying is involved.
Hey, dude, your power's being
a bug magnet. You're Bug Man.
There are, like, 100 rooms in here.
Why do we all have to share the same one?
I guess they want us to bond?
Oh, great.
Let me know how that goes, yeah?
Later.
Oh, not too bad.
Hey, we can work with this.
I guess we should choose our beds, right?
-Hey, give me that bed.
-Okay.
I love this power.
Whoo.
Did you have any idea you were different?
Before today, I mean.
Yeah.
About a year ago people started doing
the craziest things when I asked.
I always thought it was because I was
super charming but now it all makes sense.
How about you?
I don't know.
The last few months,
I've been getting a lot of bug bites.
I didn't think much of it,
and no one else noticed, of course.
One of the benefits of being invisible.
Hey,
you're not invisible to invisible girl.
I saw that butterfly she gave you.
She'd never go for a guy like me.
Never say never.
Hey, you can have this bed if you want to.
I shouldn't have just--
It's okay. This one's fine.
But maybe next time
don't do that powers thing on me.
Fair enough.
As long as you keep your bugs to yourself.
Deal.
Mind if I take the top?
My twin brother always took the top bunk
when we were kids. He's the worst.
He cheated on all of his finals.
I'm genuinely worried about our country
if he's the one who's ruling it.
He was born first by a minute,
so he gets the throne. So unfair.
I hear you.
Is your sister horrible too?
Actually, no. She's perfect in every way.
Being a second-born is bad enough,
but when you always feel
like you're second place...
It's not just that.
It's constantly feeling
like I'm being compared to her
or compared to how a princess should be.
Like, we can't have our own identities.
Exactly.
Backup phone. Smart.
Don't worry, I can keep a secret.
Learning to use your powers is
all about focus, concentration, precision.
Right now, your powers are being
controlled by hormones,
stressful situations, peer pressure,
social anxiety, physical attraction,
even loud music from an overrated band.
Now that you know what your powers are,
training is about learning
to control them.
How do we do that?
Practice.
This test is designed
to help sharpen your super senses.
Listen carefully to the voices.
-Okay, pay attention.
-
A little boy just told Santa
what he wants for Christmas. What is it?
Remember the last time we were here?
Of course.
-Not socks?
The results are in.
Are you ready to find out?
I just don't have a good feeling--
The boy is asking for...
It's not a big deal.
I'm not going to cheat.
Because he has the same answers
to the final every year.
I don't know.
"To learn to succeed,
you must first learn to fail."
Prince Tuma, you have one of the more
unique powers I've ever seen.
-Thanks.
-I understand you're quite the dog lover.
Big time! I've got five purebreds
back at the palace and they love me.
Glad you said that.
Because your powers rely
on your interactions with others,
you'll need a partner.
Bring it.
And seeing as no royal has ever been able
to train Charlie,
we thought your unique skill set
could meet the challenge.
Charlie?
Prince Tuma, meet Charlie.
If you can get him to obey your orders,
you can get anyone to follow your command.
What, what do I have to practice?
Isn't my power borrowing someone else's?
Yes, but you need to learn how
to do it for more than a few seconds.
We're gonna work on getting you
to keep them for as long as necessary.
In a pool?
I wanna introduce you to someone.
She is gonna help you with your training.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Princess Anna of Spain.
My power is breathing underwater.
And now it's yours.
-Good luck.
-
Ready?
-Come on. Lift it.
Insects aren't just drawn to you, Matteo.
You can also control them.
-
I love that you get me, James.
Honestly, I've been so missing
my Karma cycle class,
but, you know, I wasn't about to complain.
Oh, what's that?
Solar flare simulation.
Agents must be prepared
to deploy year-round,
bearing the coldest of winters
to the hottest of summers.
That artificial sun is scrumpt--
Do you reckon I can still tan
whilst I'm invisible?
Oi.
Ah, goggles. Wise choice.
Oh. Oh.
All right, James. I get it.
We're ready year-round.
All seasons. Please push stop.
You disappear, I turn it off.
Gosh, that's so annoying.
Why can't I disappear?
Remember the last time we were here?
I'm so over this.
Hey! You've got the power of persuasion.
Surely you can compel James
to return my phone.
Your fans won't care
if you don't post for 48 hours.
I've an image to maintain.
A responsibility.
What about serving your kingdom?
Firsties are the ones
with all the responsibility.
Whole point of being us is hakuna matata.
Hey, you're not the one
who has to spend their summer
running away from man's best friend.
Okay, kids, lunch is up.
Sam.
This smells toxic.
Relax. Only Sam's was poisoned.
She needs the practice.
Everything is a test. Everything.
Dang. That's cold.
Here. We can share.
Red apples are my favorite.
Thanks.
I just realized something.
I've never had lunch with other kids
at Strathmore before.
All right, I'm out. Time to train.
-Hey, come on, Charlie.
-
Oh!
- Come on, boy.
I'm gonna get malaria and die.
-No, you're not.
-You might.
Yeah, actually, you might.
-Hey.
-Hey. Sorry I've been MIA.
How's it going? What class are you taking?
You know, the ushe.
How's your summer going?
Well, not as much fun without you,
but it's gonna be awesome.
I printed out the fliers for our gig.
-
Can't wait.
I gotta go.
Yeah, okay. Uh...
Good night.
Hey, those look great.
Thanks.
You know, I've been working
for royals my entire life.
They live in their own world.
I'm just worried that someday
she's gonna forget about you and move on.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
Sam's not like that, Dad.
She's my best friend.
Hey, James. You wanted to see me?
Mom?
Teleportation?
-That's your power?
-Mm-hmm.
Next time call me a Lyft.
James said you're struggling.
Epsilon 97 red Q zero.
I'm guessing
that's not your Wi-Fi password.
Royal master code.
Opens every door in the palace.
Overrides any security measure.
As the queen and the head of the Society,
I'm the only person who has it.
I'm sharing it because I trust you.
Might wanna hold on to that chair.
We have a Batcave under our house?
Our headquarters.
No recruit is supposed to see it
until training is complete.
Wow. So you're breaking the rules.
I won't tell if you won't.
What is all this stuff?
Disrupter prototype.
Stolen from a research facility in Kyoto.
Recovered by us.
Ultrasonic elephant whistle
taken from a poaching ring in Chad.
DNA-based nano-device programmed
to target specific genetic sequences.
It can isolate
and contain cellular materials.
Our most decorated operatives.
Lots of people struggle in the beginning.
What's with the empty frame?
A former member who betrayed us.
We keep it empty as a reminder
our powers were given to us
to defend the world, not rule it.
You don't have to worry about that.
I can't even figure out
what some kid wants for Christmas.
The key to mastering your power
is mastering yourself.
It's not helpful.
I know how hard training is,
but this is worth it.
I don't know what this is.
I mean, a couple weeks ago I thought
you were banishing me to summer school,
and then I find out
that you're head of the Avengers.
I have these powers
that I don't know how to use,
and I'm supposed to defend the world?
I went through the same feelings
when I was your age.
I'm a second-born too.
What did you do?
I let go of the pressure
I was putting on myself
and allowed myself
to just be in the moment.
All I hear is noise.
Try this.
You are at one
of those royal events you love,
people, music, chitchat.
What do you do?
I tune them out.
Mm-hmm.
Now, find the sound you want to hear.
You're stronger than you know, Sam.
There's many things
that are different than a toy...
We have the results.
Are you ready to find out?
-...same answers to the final every year.
- I don't think it's a good idea.
-...Santa could bring you for Christmas.
- Fine. Your loss.
I just want my mom to get better.
The boy's mom is sick.
He's asking Santa
if she's going to get better.
-Mm-hmm. Keep going.
- Will you marry me?
A guy is proposing to his girlfriend
in the spot where they first met.
It's not a big deal.
A girl has the answers to a bio test,
but her friend doesn't want to cheat.
Mm-hmm.
- It's a boy. And a girl.
A doctor is telling a pregnant woman
that she's having...
Congratulations,
you're having twins.
...twins.
Excellent work.
See? Being second-born
doesn't mean you're second-best.
Just one question.
-Mm-hmm?
Does the boy's mom get better?
Yeah, she did.
And yours would be very proud.
Are we gonna go again?
Okay, whatever you say.
Please tell me you can't see anything!
All I see is a princess
who needs to work harder.
James, I want nothing more
than to get off this... stupid thing!
But I just can't do it.
Come on. Lift it.
Yes.
-How'd I do this time?
You were under for ten minutes.
That's the longest
you've held on to my powers yet.
Yes.
Brava. Quite the improvement.
Hey, Charlie!
No class for you today, Prince Tuma.
Really? Sweet.
-Yeah. Charlie's sick.
-Oh.
He ate something
that didn't agree with him.
Hey, buddy.
Charlie.
I didn't know that treat
would make you sick.
I was just trying to be nice.
I didn't know what else to do.
Everyone always just listens
to what I tell them.
Okay.
Look, look, look.
-This is my fault.
-
Clearly, physical duress
doesn't trigger your powers.
I got something really special
for you, Roxy. Okay?
-Oh, my phone.
-Yeah.
What are you doing?
I know you missed your followers
over the past few weeks.
I'm sure that they would love
to say hi, right?
You're bluffing.
I mean, you don't even know my password.
With the click of a button,
I can create the most sophisticated
interactive obstacle course in the world.
I think I got this.
No. They can't see me like this.
James, why are you being so mean?
-And we are live in four, three, two, one!
-I mean. I mean, look at me. No. No. No!
No!
-Well done. Same time tomorrow.
Can you please log off?
Oh, I was never online.
Reception's terrible down here.
Everything okay?
I turned myself invisible today.
That's great.
But it's not.
I'm able to do all these really cool
things, but no one will see me.
So, what does it matter?
I forgot, livestream or it's not real.
Performance is part of being a royal.
I've lived my whole life online.
It's always been me.
Why can't you be you without all that?
Because I genuinely don't know
where to start.
Well, I can't help you with that.
Only because you have to figure that out
for yourself.
-Yeah.
-
How do I look?
Awful.
It's a new record.
Come on.
-
Yes!
- Awesome!
-Bro!
-
That was awesome.
-Thank you.
-Charlie! You're all better!
Aw.
Hey, Sam. I'm here. Got the gear.
Super pumped.
Hey, come see our show.
- Attention, trainees.
Suit up and meet
in the loading dock immediately.
Attention, trainees. Suit up and meet
in the loading dock immediately!
Let's go! Get in. Get in. Get in. Get in.
Let's go!
There's been a break-in
at the royal treasury.
If the thieves steal the crown jewels,
they could be sold on the black market
for billions to buy
weapons of mass destruction.
-So super low stakes.
-Our first mission.
We got this.
Hey, come to our show.
We're on soon. Thanks.
Come on, Sam. Where are you?
Hey, come to our show. We're on soon.
Your mission is
to protect the jewels at all costs.
Wow! Look at that!
-Those are some big rocks.
-Yeppers.
You guys stay here and guard
the jewels. I saw one of the thieves.
I'm going after him.
She's gonna need backup.
They aren't getting all the glory.
I guess it's just you and me.
Or it's just you.
Hey, guys.
Wait up.
I saw him. He was wearing a hood.
He's got to be in there.
Now what?
Maybe we should just wait for James.
No way. If we take this guy down,
James is gonna be super impressed.
It's so dark.
I can't see anything.
Hey, look.
- Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Watch out!
You did it.
Yeah, I did. Thanks.
That was really smart.
Uh, guys. That's my swim coach.
Wait, why would your swim coach
wanna steal the jewels?
The jewels!
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-This is bad.
-Oh, you think?
In a matter of minutes,
you managed to disobey my orders,
lose a priceless national treasure,
and put yourself in a potentially
deadly situation with no plan.
Your degree of failure is remarkable.
Thank you for your help, Princess Anna.
Of course. Anytime.
Wait, I'm confused. Where are the jewels?
Oh, where they've always been,
in the real treasury.
Congratulations,
you've all failed the test.
I'm canceling tomorrow's training.
Take the day to consider the consequences
had this been real.
Class dismissed.
Where were you?
I'm sorry. I couldn't make it.
Yeah, I know. I was there. What happened?
I just couldn't.
-Sam, what's going on? Talk to me.
-I really wanna tell you...
But I can't.
I gotta go.
You okay?
I don't wanna talk about it.
None of us are getting in.
Catherine said, "No matter what obstacles
you face, nothing is impossible."
She also said
not everyone's gonna make the cut.
Definitely one of those people.
Hey, you deserve to be here
as much as anyone else.
I've been going to Strathmore
for three years.
You didn't even know I existed
until this summer.
But that wasn't your fault. That was mine.
And we know you now.
Until we all get our minds wiped.
What if that really happens?
We'll forget we even have powers.
We'll forget the whole summer.
Do we really want that?
No way.
Hanging with you guys has been
the best thing that's ever happened to me.
Well, if they're gonna make us forget,
we can at least
make this a day to remember.
I have an idea. Come on.
Told you I'd bring the party.
Is this one as fun as the one you threw
at your old school?
Well, there are no explosions yet, so...
How'd that happen anyway?
My friends and I were messing around
in the lab.
Told them to mix a bunch of chemicals,
as a joke.
You know, see if we could start a fire.
Didn't know I was using my power on them.
Can't really use that excuse anymore.
If I told someone to do something and
something bad happened, it was on them.
But now I realize it's on me.
Took you a while, but you got there.
Now I'm starting to grow on you.
Maybe a little. Like a fungus.
Yeah, like a fungus.
Thanks.
I want a pink one. Are they poisoned?
They're all the same.
If you go down, we all do.
We should do this again.
Maybe, like, Saturday?
Can't. Sister's stupid coronation.
You guys have fun.
Yeah, must suck going to the hottest event
of the season.
With the prettiest dresses.
It's definitely not the hottest event
of the season.
Just instead of only Illyria
obsessing over my sister for an hour,
the whole world gets to.
I can always make Sam invite us.
But mind control would be
a messed up thing to do to a friend.
I mean, if you guys really wanna go,
I could use the company.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Okay. Never do that again.
Oh, my God!
You guys go ahead. We'll catch up.
That was the best day ever.
Totally, so why are you sad?
It just hit me. I'm leaving soon,
which means I'm not going to be here.
After training, it's back to my kingdom
and my stupid brother.
We never even got a chance
to hang out at your palace.
How about now?
Come on.
Can't believe you talked me
into missing curfew.
We could get into so much trouble.
I like it.
They tightened security
for the upcoming coronation.
We can't go through the front gate
without my mom finding out.
Come on.
Epsilon 97 red Q zero.
Wow!
My dad converted the tower into a studio.
He and my uncle Edmond would come up here
and jam all the time.
He always said, "Snowflake, it's good
to rule, but it's more fun to rock."
It was either piano or ballet.
Had a lot of free time while everyone
doted on my precious brother.
-Sam?
Mike, wait!
No. Mike, wait! Wait!
I'm sorry about the gig.
Yeah, and now you're in a band
with somebody else?
No, she's just a girl from school.
-Oh, right. You mean another princess.
-It's not like that. I can explain.
Go ahead.
I--
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Later, Your Highness.
Everything okay?
We should get back.
My mom really wanted me
to do the whole ballet thing,
but I'm happy I picked piano.
It's so much fun to just jam,
and, anyway, tulle makes me itch.
Mm-hmm.
-
Really, James? Kidnapping after curfew?
I mean, I get it.
Lesson three, everything's a test.
- It's not a simulation!
-Freeze!
-
Sam?
Another time...
Snowflake.
What happened?
There was this really scary guy,
and he had powers too,
and he threw January and Sam
without even touching them.
Go to your rooms.
Lock the doors right now.
-Who was he?
-He's a very dangerous telekinetic.
-Yeah, no kidding.
-We have to go after him.
That's out of the question.
He called me "Snowflake."
Only my father did that.
-Stand down, Sam.
-How did he know?
That's an order.
Okay. Go to your rooms and stay there.
Sam! Hey! Wait!
Who are you?
Stop!
-Hello, James.
-Surrender.
You know I won't.
You can't win. There's too many of us.
All I need is one.
-
James!
- January!
Sam!
You knock out the original,
-you knock out the power.
- James!
Tell me who you are.
For the last ten years,
it has been "Inmate 34."
January!
- Sam!
But before your mother
took my name away from me...
James!
...I was your favorite uncle.
January!
My turn.
Hey.
I've got your back, always.
Let's go find the others.
All right. Here we go.
Two bumps, and up.
Radio the university
and let them know we're ten out.
Will do.
All right, just hooking him up here.
Vitals are stable.
We'll start O2 if we need to.
Gotcha. I'm right behind you.
Let 'em know we're on our way.
This is all my fault.
Hey, no.
You did what you could to stop him.
James is in intensive care.
You put his life and yours in danger
because you disobeyed an order.
Is he really my uncle?
-Sam, it's complicated.
-I'll make it simple.
There was no plane crash.
The empty frame on the wall, the man
who betrayed the Society, that was Edmond.
Is my father still alive too?
No, darling.
He's not.
Edmond wanted to be king,
so he murdered your father.
I uncovered the truth
before he claimed the throne,
but nobody could know.
Trust in the royal family
would've been shattered.
So you lied.
I did the only thing I could.
He killed my dad.
And my husband.
I stripped Edmond of his identity.
I locked him up in our most secure prison.
It's no coincidence
he escaped so close to the coronation.
He wants the throne, and he wants revenge.
I wanna see him.
Mom, please.
Hey.
-Snowflake.
You wanna learn how to play?
Come on over here.
So all you have to do is you just
strum the guitar like that. Can you do it?
You're officially a rock star, yeah.
Catherine?
Have you come to gloat?
Make it quick.
Hello, Sam.
Uncle Edmond.
It's been a long time
since I've heard my name.
How could you kill your brother?
It's an electric cage.
And this collar projects a field
that nullifies my power.
Come closer.
I loved my brother, you know?
But great causes demand great sacrifices.
You wanted power?
I wanted to tear down the monarchy
so that the people could live as citizens,
not subjects.
But your father wanted to wait.
He said that change takes time.
But that way nothing gets done.
So you murdered him.
You will never forgive me
for what I've done, Snowflake.
At least now you understand why.
El?
Sam.
Didn't realize you were back.
Summer school was a bust.
Hey, at least now you can help me
prepare for the coronation.
Just please don't be late for once.
You have no idea what I'm dealing with.
Do you think you have it tough?
You get to do whatever you like,
and I have to live up to everybody's
expectations because you never do.
I never asked you to do that for me.
You didn't have to.
What is that supposed to mean?
You were so young when dad died,
and you took it so hard.
I chose to be the perfect princess,
so you could just be free to be a kid.
And sure, there are some parts
of the kingdom that feel old-fashioned,
but I'm about to be
in a position to enact real change.
That means something to me,
and every time that you yell,
"Down with the monarchy,"
you are rebelling
against everything that I stand for!
I didn't realize
it was going to get this real, this fast.
Do you think Sam's coming back?
Maybe, or maybe not.
I mean, she almost got herself killed.
She almost got James killed.
Who even was that crazy guy?
I have a bad feeling we're gonna find out
sooner rather than later.
Well, what are we meant to do now?
Keep practicing.
They'll give us a new teacher.
-And what about the coronation?
-Sam said she'd get us in.
We should be there for her. Right?
You awake?
Yeah. I can't sleep either.
Yeah, I know why.
You're too excited to hang out
with Roxana at the coronation.
Be quiet.
What I'm actually thinking about
is what's gonna happen after that.
If we're gonna get in.
Into the Society?
Yeah.
For the first time in my life,
I feel I could do something
that actually matters.
And let's be honest,
royalty by day, superhero by night
sounds pretty dope.
No matter what happens,
I'm glad I got to meet you.
Hey, don't laugh.
I'm not.
I feel the same way.
This has been one crazy summer.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
I'm a little sore still, but I'll be okay.
I brought you a snack.
Figured you could use a break
from hospital food.
Is this a bagel?
You really are trying to kill me.
Oh, don't worry. It's gluten-free.
-You remembered my allergy. Put it there.
- Mm-hmm.
I feel terrible about what happened.
You told me not to go after Edmond,
and I should've listened.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't even be in here.
Well, I am always right,
but I forgive you.
And I'm not entirely convinced
that Edmond was working alone.
We may not have seen the end of this.
I was just starting to find my place...
you know?
I finally meet royals
I actually get along with,
and I was figuring out my powers.
And then it all falls apart.
Sam...
I'm a second-born too, remember?
I know what it's like to feel alone.
And, thankfully, there's, like, 20 of me
to keep me company, but...
You're meant for great things.
I really wanna believe that.
Well, I do, and you should.
And when the moment comes,
you'll be ready.
Enough of this mushy stuff.
Give me my bagel
and get out of here, okay?
Yeah.
Happy birthday, darling.
You look like a queen.
What if I'm not ready?
Can I tell you a secret?
I wasn't ready either.
Act like the leader
they believe you to be.
That's how you become one.
-Your Lordship, please. Thank you.
-
Props to Sam for coming through.
It's hard to impress me,
and even I'm impressed.
Every single important royal
in the world is here.
Is this not the most
beautiful thing you've ever seen?
It is.
Too bad James can't be here.
Hey, where's Sam anyway?
Probably helping Eleanor get ready.
Hey, excuse me, ma'am?
I'd love one of those mints.
It's my last one.
Please.
That's weird.
My powers aren't working.
Where's January?
This is a restricted area.
Oh, hi.
The queen sent me
to check on the prisoner.
We're gonna need confirmation.
Open the door, now.
The plan is working.
The apples were a brilliant idea.
Sorry, I'm late.
I had to steal Tuma's power.
Nicely done.
Epsilon 97 red Q zero.
None of them have any idea
that we're working together.
They truly suspect nothing.
Phase two.
Hey, there you are. Did you take my power?
Come with me. All of you.
Where? I don't wanna miss the coronation.
Yeah, you do. Where's Sam?
-How should I know? Give me back my p--
-Don't speak.
The rest of you too.
Scanning all systems.
Emergency alert systems deactivated.
Communications deactivated.
Stop.
The alarms and external communication's
been disconnected.
I disabled the master code.
Smart.
Even if Catherine figures out what's
going on, she won't be able to stop us.
We can still move in and out of here
using this pin.
Come with me.
Get in the cell. All of you.
You'll thank me later.
Matteo?
January, report.
I put the second-borns in your cell.
You're clear all the way to the target.
Excellent.
Everything is going according to plan.
Proceed to phase three.
We have a straggler.
Epsilon 97 red Q zero!
Sam knows something's up.
Catch her before she becomes a problem.
Security system linked.
- Nano-device activated.
Calibrating DNA target parameters.
There are moments in the life of every
leader and every parent that stand apart.
This is one of them.
I could not hope
for a more deserving successor...
and a more perfect daughter.
Hard way it is.
Mike! Mike, I know you're in there!
-Mike!
-Shouldn't you be at the coronation?
I need your help. It's important.
What? More important than our gig?
-Go ask your new best friend.
-Mike, I'm serious. People are in danger.
It's an emergency.
What kind of emergency?
I can't tell you.
Sounds familiar. Bye.
Wait. No, okay. I--
Remember how I could read the numbers
from really far away
and smell what you had for lunch?
Yeah, so?
Well, it turns out I have powers,
and summer school was a training program
for a secret society of royal superhumans
run by my mom.
My uncle killed my dad. He escaped jail.
My new best friend is his spy,
and she can mind control people.
And the palace is on lockdown,
and they're about to do something really
horrible to everyone at the coronation.
That was the worst story ever.
Thank you all for being here.
I've been preparing for this day
my entire life.
Queen of Illyria
is a great responsibility.
Stop.
I love this power.
Drop it.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to hurt you,
but I can't let you ruin things either.
You pretended to be my friend
so that I would show you
how to sneak into the palace.
Sorry, Sam. I made a deal with Edmond.
I help him, he gets rid of my brother.
We've been working together all along.
I deserve to rule.
And I can't kill my brother myself.
That would make me an awful person.
I'm just looking out for my kingdom.
Why did Edmond wanna get caught?
Aren't we nosy?
Let's just say, everyone of royal birth
at your sister's coronation
is about to have a really bad day.
I don't think I properly introduced you
to my best friend, Mike.
Bull's-eye.
I'm glad I believed you.
-Mike, I'm so sorry.
-It's okay.
All right. What now?
I have to save my family.
Wrong. We have to save your family.
Look, I know it's dangerous,
and I don't have powers,
but friends don't let friends
save the world by themselves.
Okay.
-You have a Batcave under your house?
-That's what I said.
Come on.
Sam!
The scary guy's on the loose.
And January--
I know. We have to go after Edmond.
-He's been working with January all along.
-Wait, who's Edmond?
-The scary guy. Also, her not-dead uncle.
-I knew that guy would come back.
-And who are you?
-Mike Kleinberg.
So...
He's my best friend.
Edmond wanted to get caught.
Coming after me at school was a ruse.
He needed something from this place.
Something only the Society--
DNA-based nano-device,
programmed to target specific genes.
-It's gone.
-One more time using small words.
Think of a device
that only works on certain people
who share specific genetic traits.
Like hazel eyes or freckles.
January said that everyone of royal birth
is about to have a bad day.
Edmond is going to unleash the device
at the coronation.
It'll wipe out everyone with a royal
bloodline, including my family.
-Well, we have to call for help.
- There's no one left to call.
James is in the hospital.
My mom is leading the coronation.
This one's on us.
There's a way
we can use the device to stop him.
You want us to go up against him?
We have something he doesn't.
He's alone. We are a team.
He's more powerful than any of us,
but he's not more powerful than all of us.
-Who's with me?
- Let's do this.
Obviously, I'm in.
I can't sit this one out.
Edmond wore a collar in custody.
It radiates a field that cancels powers.
So, we just have to
put it around his neck?
Without him killing us with his pinkie.
Or we get the other collars from his cell,
and we build a trap.
Here's the plan.
We split up.
That way he won't see us coming.
Tuma, you climb up the elevator cable.
Why can't I ride it?
He'll hear it coming
and send it crashing to the ground.
-Oh.
-I'll take the north air duct.
Sweet.
I'll free-climb the side of the palace.
Sounds dangerous.
Relax. I'm invisible.
I'm just gonna take the stairs.
All right. Well, what about me?
You and Matteo
are the most crucial part of the plan.
Ready for deployment.
Don't do it.
Eleanor hasn't done anything to you.
And neither have
any of the people in there.
This is the new beginning.
Freedom. And not only for Illyria,
but for the other kingdoms as well.
It's a world without royals.
Isn't that what you want?
Not like this.
This isn't freedom.
It's murder.
Time is running out, Snowflake.
And you cannot defeat me.
Not by myself.
Disarm the device. Surrender now.
You're not powerful enough to control me.
I know, dude, but I made you look.
Give it. Give it. I'm right here!
-Tuma!
-Roxana!
Come on!
Yes!
Do you swear
to uphold the laws of Illyria?
I do.
Hi.
-Not gonna happen.
We brought the collars from your cell.
Your powers aren't gonna work in here.
And without your powers, it's game over.
Give me that or we're both gonna die.
You programmed this thing
to target royals.
But we reprogrammed it to trap you.
Activation imminent.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Subject acquired.
Sam! It's over.
Your plan worked. We got him.
Rise a queen.
Congratulations.
Nothing is impossible
if you work together.
Welcome to The Secret Society.
I had faith in you guys
from the beginning.
Go ahead, take your pins.
You've earned them.
Hey, Charlie. Give me a kiss,
give me a kiss, give me a kiss.
I've gotta say, James, dope idea
having me practice on Charlie.
I have a confession to make.
Your power only works on humans, not dogs.
Charlie obeys your commands
because he likes you.
So what was the point?
To make you care about something
other than yourself.
El.
I just wanna tell you how grateful
I am for what you and your friends did.
Mom told me everything.
She doesn't want
any more secrets in our family.
Well, it was my turn to protect you.
I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
You're not wrong
that some things do need to change.
For my first order as queen,
I'm giving the people of Illyria a choice
of having a parliament
alongside the monarchy.
We're more alike than you think.
A few hours ago, a bank in Geneva
considered impenetrable was robbed.
Our intel suggests the funds may be used
to finance a coup.
We recovered a partial fingerprint.
It matched to our database.
As you know, we have Edmond in custody,
but January remains free.
She left that print on purpose.
It's a message.
"Come and get me if you can."
You're going to do just that.
The jet is fueled.
Whoa. We have a jet?
-Wheels up in ten.
Be careful out there.
We got this, Mom.
I know you do.
I've trained some very impressive
second-born royals in my day,
but this class, they may just be
our most promising operatives yet.
Pretty cool, huh?
Well, what are you waiting for?
A royal invitation? Let's go.
Get in now
To meet me
With you
-
Yeah I'm coming for you